I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame where all is spread
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
It will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I'm over
Don't kill your walls, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the changes in power
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions apart
The golden end is still wrong, but the lowest
The pain that makes us too human after all
Don't want to see before the good show
About the precious one
This car may respond to the call
Don't come up
From under here, no matter what
Wait, sister
Hey, Lakis, headquarters is checking in
They want an update
Now of all times
It figures
It's always when I'm in the middle of eating
No, this can't be happening
So, here we are, Yuichi
Reliving your most traumatic memory and detail
Right down to the blood splatters on the floor
Tomoe, you're alive
Because of you, she's dead now
Is that you, brother?
I'm sorry, Mirai
I didn't mean to wake you up
You didn't
How are you feeling?
Not too bad
I think it's gonna be a good day for us
I do, too
I bet you're hungry
How about I scrounge up something for you to eat?
Okay?
Brother, why don't you leave me here to fend for myself
So you can move on with your life
Don't start with this
Taking care of you is my duty
But if things don't change, you'll end up dead, too
No buts, Mirai
I'm gonna make sure we both survive
You don't mean that
Not really
At night, I hear you cry
About how much you want to leave
You've grown to hate me
You wish I'd just die already
Why?
Why would you say that?
Because despite how noble you try to be
Deep down, you're a selfish human
Who only thinks of himself
Isn't that right, Shioka Mizuki?
Now I get it
You're the demon
Bingo
But I was right about your thoughts, wasn't I?
I've seen every shameful thing
That's floated through your little brain
I wonder what your sister would say
If she knew the truth
Shut the hell up
Interesting
At least one of them appears to be putting up a fight
It's good to see you
Even if you did run off and leave us to die with the vampires
It's not a good idea to imitate people I care about
Well then
I thought I'd be able to shake you up by touching on a sore spot
But you don't appear the least bit rattled
Now I wonder, why is that?
You're not the first demon who's tried to mess with my head
So just cut the crap and hand over your power already
Mika
Oh, I see what's going on
You managed to defeat a low-ranking demon like Mio
And now you think you've got what it takes to tame a being with actual power
I could possess your heart and mind without the slightest effort
You talk big
But I'm not giving up until I've got a contract with you
If you've got so much strength, then prove it to me
Hmm
You've taken up my blade in search of the demon's might
The question is why
I want revenge
Because you've lost someone important to you?
That's right
I lost the only family I ever had
That must have been difficult
Very well then
I can see the desire for revenge burning inside you
I can offer you unlimited power to achieve it
Yes
But it's not quite that simple
Sorry, you
To get our strength
You'll have to give yourself over and succumb to your desire for vengeance
Your unjustly murdered friend is right
I'd have to possess you to give you the kind of power you want
No, wait!
You
You're not gonna run off and ditch us again, are you?
You can't just abandon your family
Brother, you would never do something so dumb
Now that we're reunited, say you'll live here with us forever
Yeah, stay with us, we miss you
Ah, there it is
Your weakness
You have love in your heart and that's what's holding you back
We worship desire
We can't stand love
Yoichi
Kimizuki
Shinoa
Your new friends
Forget about them
You can't become a champion of revenge if you're worried about others
But my friends
Don't you think it's unfair that we're dead and you're making a new family?
You left us behind and now you've moved on
Going to school, training, and making new friends
You've almost managed to completely forget about us, haven't you?
I have not!
I've never forgotten!
Then forget your new friends and stay with us
Remember, we're the only family you've ever had
Shut your mouth
It's the only way you'll get the strength to avenge us
Stop it
You're gonna submit yourself to revenge now
Go to hell!
Stop trying to confuse me, you bastard!
I don't just need your strength to get revenge
There's more to it
My aim is bigger
I want enough power to protect everything and everyone!
This is the trouble with humans
Your emotions are too complicated
Love for your friends and fear for their safety
Compete against your desire for revenge
I like you
Your spirit is strong
I'll agree to follow you as long as it stays that way
But if I detect weakness in your heart for even a moment
I'll take over your body and soul
All right, I guess that's fair
My name is Ashura Maru
If you need power, all you have to do is call for me
Ashura Maru?
Oh, and since you're going to be my master
Let me give you some insider information as a gift
Information?
There's something odd about your composition
You appear to be human, but about 10% of you is something different
Could the humans be doing strange experiments on you or something?
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't trust your own kind
Believe me when I tell you mankind is more devious than vampires and demons combined
Though, it does feel a little weird saying that to a human
Wait, explain yourself
What are you suggesting?
Very well
Contract is now complete
From this day forward, I shall lend you my strength and abilities
Open your eyes
Fan the flames of desire that burn inside of you
And forge a blood-stained path in this world
You're awake
How you feelin', you?
I'm okay
I beat the demon
I wouldn't get too cocky
You took your sweet time subjugating the damn thing
You got a cursed deer too?
Of course I did
And Yoichi?
So then, who are you?
You're the one who called me, Yoichi
If you want to avenge your sister's death, you need a strong set of cursed gear to wield
Oh, that's right
I picked up a weapon and was going to make a contract with...
I see
That's what you are
A demon
That's right
It's pretty mean you chose to look like this
Just wait until you see my true form
Yeah, I bet it's pretty nasty
So, it seems we have a bit of a problem
Huh?
I've poured over your heart and soul
You want to strike back at those who hurt you, but that desire is too weak
Your soul is gentle
And kind
You have great love for others
These are all qualities that I despise
Wait, maybe you should look deeper
Cause I do want to avenge my sister
You lie
In fact, the strongest feeling you have is the relief that you survived the attack
No, that's not true
Not to mention, you'd make a terrible fighter
You're afraid of conflict
And the thought of your friends and family getting hurt
You're weak
You don't have the courage to take a life
How are you supposed to get revenge if you aren't capable of killing?
What I really mean is you're a coward
Just a child without a backbone
A weakling
You don't have the guts to fight for your life
You wouldn't make a suitable master
You're the most pathetic human being I've ever met
Oh man, this is not good
Looks like Yoichi didn't have the strength to overcome possession
But I guess having two out of three students pass the Black Demon tryout
Isn't that bad at all
Huh?
Hey, wait, where'd he go?
One
Two
Three
Four little humans all for me
Dammit, but they've each got cursed gears too
Power-hungry humans are such a pain in the ass
My bow
All right
Now that you two have both got your cursed gear
It's time for your first mission
There's a human-eating demon loose somewhere in this room
You, Kimizuki
It's up to you guys to deal with it
Show that bastard who's in control
They'll be my appetizers
Then the real feast will begin
Yoichi!
Well, great
Looks like this demon is coming at us with full force
Yoichi must have just been a snack to whet its appetite
Lieutenant Colonel
May I share my opinion?
Please, no
Quiet
The situation's getting out of control
Hey, Gurren!
How are we supposed to deal with this?
Yoichi is still one of us
Look at him
Your classmate's body assist a vessel now
The only way to save Yoichi is to destroy it
What the hell, man?
There's no way I'm gonna kill one of my friends
Don't you get soft on me
This is the Moon Demon Company
Extermination is your job
Or are you guys all talking
Just here to play around with cursed gear
If you want to get killed, that's on you
But that monster's not your friend anymore
Damn it
If you're serious about using those weapons
Then show me you've got what it takes to be a soldier
Damn it, Yoichi
Sorry, but
You're going down!
What the hell was that?
You!
Let Yoichi go, you monster
He's one of us!
Yes!
You idiot!
Don't let up
The demon's not inside the weapon anymore
It's in his body
Don't do it!
We can still save him!
No!
Interesting
You won't touch me because of the body I'm in
Joichi!
I know you're in there!
Don't let this stupid demon get the best of you!
Snap out of it!
We're supposed to kill vampires together, remember?
Lieutenant Colonel!
These boys are going to get themselves killed!
They're not ready for this!
Please don't make them kill Yoichi!
He's their friend!
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh Joichi!
He's their friend!
Aww!
You always act like they're so cool, but you've got a soft spot for these two problem students.
You've gotten attached, haven't you?
Lieutenant Colonel!
Why don't you step in and kill him then?
That'll save the others from being racked with guilt!
Oh, I see.
You've got no intention of getting your hands dirty either.
Let me guess, you're just too cute for this as well.
Joichi!
Get yourself together!
together you're strong enough to beat this thing it's too late now die
do it I won't kill a comrade but I won't abandon one either if you're she's still
alive in there then you won't be able to shoot me when you've watched your family die in front of
you there's no way that you could ever kill a friend are you crazy you'll have to come back
or shoot me snap out of it yoichi die yoichi are you gonna stay under that bed and watch
your sister be killed or take charge and stop it this is your last chance to take control
yoichi listen no matter what happens don't come out from under here
i'm sorry but i can't stay no more hiding i'm not gonna run away from my fears anymore
that's why i need the ability to protect those i care about i want to be able to keep them safe from
harm only then can i make sure nothing like this ever happens again give me that power you demon
that's enough you did a good job i shot at you
what's that hell no i don't really give a damn if one of these kids ends up biting it you say that but
you look like you were really starting to sweat there towards the end of it
you have a rare gift the guilt you felt for not helping your sister has kept you from living your
life but i think today you overcame that maybe now you'll be able to reach your full potential
you have a new reason to live from now on your job is to protect the people who saved your life
today forget revenge don't get hung up on something so pointless same goes for you idiot
forget about your previous friends and loved ones huh don't be read the moon demon company is the only
family family you'll have now you're gonna put us first even before your own life got it
the past means nothing
it's the future that matters stupid current
okay well you've all got cursed gear and you almost work like a team today
i suppose we should test you out on the front line to see what you're really made of seriously that's
right we've got intel that suggests vampires from the kanzai region are planning on reclaiming shinjuku
it's our job to investigate the area we're finally gonna get to hunt vampires um shouldn't we have
some more training first we don't even get a break after all this i think these lazy kids are going
to be the death of me we'll be arriving in tokyo shortly we expect attacks from the japanese imperial demon
army near ikebukuro shinjuku and shibuya please maintain caution did you hear that well mika
we're going to shinjuku first
foreign
i need
You read love tonight, I got green light
Kaki-wake-ta-neon-to, koji-age-ta-reizun-ga, tata-heko-ni-na-la
Come and break it down for me, a river will fall
Piano song 1
See you next time
shiny
conspekts
Next time on Seraph of the End, Mitsuba's squad.